<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Music Widget</string>
    <string name="app_name_listen">Listen Widget</string>
    <string name="music_widget_3D_provider_label">Music</string>
    <string name="music_widget_3D_provider_label_listen">Listen</string>
    <string name="dummy_settings_label">Dummy Widget Settings</string>
    <string name="widget_name">Music</string>
    <string name="widget_name_listen">Listen</string>
    <string name="music_info_loading">Searching for music...</string>
    <string name="go_application">Tap to go to the music application.</string>
    <string name="go_application_listen">Tap to go to the Listen application.</string>
    <string name="no_music_found">No music found. Tap to go to the music application.</string>
    <string name="no_music_found_listen">No music found. Tap to go to the Listen application.</string>
    <string name="no_sdcard_found">No SD card found. Tap to go to the music application.</string>
    <string name="no_sdcard_found_listen">No SD card found. Tap to go to the Listen application.</string>
    <string name="no_sd_card">No SD card. Tap to go to music application.</string>
    <string name="no_sd_card_listen">No SD card. Tap to go to Listen application.</string>
    <string name="sd_card_unavailible">SD card is unavailable because it is being used as USB storage. Tap to go to music application.</string>
    <string name="sd_card_unavailible_listen">SD card is unavailable because it is being used as USB storage. Tap to go to Listen application.</string>
    <string name="sd_card_eject_found">SD card unmounted. Tap to go to music application.</string>
    <string name="sd_card_eject_found_listen">SD card unmounted. Tap to go to Listen application.</string>
    <string name="phone_storage_unavailible">Your content is unavailable because your phone is being used as USB storage. Disconnect USB to access your content. Tap to go to the music application.</string>
    <string name="fail_to_read_both_storages">Your content is unavailable because a storage error occurred. Tap to go to the music application.</string>
    <string name="no_music_in_queue">Choose songs from your library to play some music. Tap to go to the music application.</string>
    <string name="no_music_in_queue_listen">Choose songs from your library to play some music. Tap to go to Listen application.</string>
    <string name="durationformat">%2$d:%5$02d</string>
    <string name="durationformat_h">%1$d:%3$02d:%5$02d</string>
    <string name="htc_private_app">Music widget</string>
    <string name="music_in_dmc_mode">Music is currently being controlled remotely. Tap to open the connected media music controller.</string>
    <string name="music_in_dmc_mode_listen">Listen is currently being controlled remotely. Tap to open the connected media music controller.</string>
    <string name="rosie_widget_release_date">2011/02/01 00:00</string>
    <string name="widget_detail_description">Control music playback and view album art for the current track.</string>
    <string name="recent_playlist">Recently played</string>
    <string name="no_recent_playlist">No recently played music</string>
    <string name="no_music_available">No music available</string>
</resources>
