<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WLAN Hotspot</string>
    <string name="kddi_app_name">WLAN tethering</string>
    <string name="intro_title">Portable WLAN Hotspot</string>
    <string name="intro_line1">"Portable WLAN Hotspot can share this phone's 3G Internet connection with your PC via WLAN."</string>
    <string name="intro_line2">After the Portable WLAN Hotspot is started on this phone, your PC can connect to it and then start using the Internet.</string>
    <string name="kddi_intro_line1">"WLAN tethering can share this phone's Internet connection with your PC via WLAN."</string>
    <string name="kddi_intro_line2">After the WLAN tethering is started on this phone, your PC can connect to it and then start using the Internet.</string>
    <string name="vzw_intro_line1">"Mobile Hotspot can share this phone's 3G Internet connection with your PC via WLAN."</string>
    <string name="sprint_intro_line1">"Sprint Mobile Hotspot can share this phone's 3G/4G Internet connection with your device via WLAN."</string>
    <string name="tmo_intro_line1">"%s allows you to instantly create a fast WLAN connection using T-Mobile's advanced data network."</string>
    <string name="hutch_intro_line1">"PocketWifi™ can share this phone's 3G Internet connection with your PC via WLAN."</string>
    <string name="guild_line1">1. Turn on WLAN on your PC.</string>
    <string name="sprint_guild_line1">1. Enable WLAN on the device you want to connect to your Sprint Mobile Hotspot.</string>
    <string name="sprint_guild_line2">2. Find \"%s\" in the list of WLAN networks.</string>
    <string name="tmo_guild_line3" formatted="false">3. Select \"%s\" in the list of WLAN networks and enter \"%s\" in the security field.</string>
    <string name="tmo_guild_line3_open">3. Select \"%s.\" in the list of WLAN networks.</string>
    <string name="kddi_wifi_router_status_starting">Starting WLAN tethering...</string>
    <string name="wifi_channel">WLAN channel</string>
    <string name="is_dialog_mms_content_tianshan">Starting a WLAN hotspot or Internet sharing connection will interrupt ongoing sending or receiving of MMS messages. Would you like to continue?</string>
    <string name="vzw_wifi_turnoff_warning_message">WLAN is currently active. WLAN and Mobile Hotspot cannot run at the same time. WLAN will be turned off.</string>
    <string name="usc_remind_dialog_title">Introduction for Portable WLAN Hotspot</string>
    <string name="usc_remind_dialog_message">"Portable WLAN hotspot allows your Android-powered device to be used as a mobile hotspot for up to five devices using your phone’s data connection. If using this service, you should secure the connection to deny unauthorized access. This service consumes battery power and increases your data usage.
This service requires a subscription to the applicable modem plan. Please ensure you have subscribed to the appropriate data plan prior to use. Call 1-877-872-2249 if you need assistance.
Use of service constitutes acceptance of the "<a href="http://www.uscellular.com/uscellular/common/common.jsp?path=/android/modem_feature.html">Smartphone Modem Terms</a>.</string>
    <string name="vzw_lte_intro_line1">"Mobile Hotspot can share this phone's 4G Internet connection with your PC via WLAN."</string>
    <string name="kt_intro_line1">"Portable WLAN Hotspot can share this phone's 3G/WiBro 4G Internet connection with your PC via WLAN."</string>
</resources>
