<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Updater</string>
    <string name="message">While your phone is updating, you cannot make emergency calls. Your phone will restart during update.</string>
    <string name="confirm_label">A system update is ready for download and installation.</string>
    <string name="confirm_message">Your phone will be reset to factory settings. All data will be erased. Please back up your data before installation.</string>
    <string name="download_later">Download later</string>
    <string name="download_FW">System update</string>
    <string name="progress_label">Downloading updates</string>
    <string name="btn_cancel_download">Cancel download</string>
    <string name="state_running">Download in progress. This may take some time.</string>
    <string name="state_stop">Download successful</string>
    <string name="unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="megabyte">MB</string>
    <string name="verifypackage">Verifying update package…</string>
    <string name="label_remind_me_later">Remind me later</string>
    <string name="msg_install_warning">Your phone will be reset to factory settings. All data will be erased.</string>
    <string name="category_software_update">Software updates</string>
    <string name="title_periodic_checkin">Scheduled check</string>
    <string name="summary_periodic_checkin">Go online and check for updates according to schedule from server</string>
    <string name="msg_data_warning_periodic">Using this service over your mobile network connection may result in additional fees from your wireless provider if you do not have an unlimited data plan. Enable scheduled check?</string>
    <string name="title_warning_periodic_off">Turn off scheduled check</string>
    <string name="msg_warning_periodic_off">We suggest that you keep this option enabled in order to keep your phone software up to date. The check messages consume a very small amount of data, are anonymous and do not include any personal information. Turn off scheduled check?</string>
    <string name="btn_turn_off">Turn off</string>
    <string name="btn_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="btn_no">No</string>
    <string name="btn_check_now">Check now</string>
    <string name="msg_checking">Checking…</string>
    <string name="btn_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_up_to_date">Your phone is up to date</string>
    <string name="msg_up_to_date">There are no updates available for your phone.</string>
    <string name="title_downloading">Downloading system update</string>
    <string name="msg_downloading">Your phone is downloading the software updates.</string>
    <string name="title_download_prompt">A system update is available</string>
    <string name="msg_download_prompt">Would you like to download the following system software update?</string>
    <string name="label_download_now">Download via any available data connection</string>
    <string name="label_download_now_4g">Download via mobile network or Wi-Fi or 4G</string>
    <string name="label_download_via_wifi">Download via Wi-Fi or cable only</string>
    <string name="btn_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="btn_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="msg_data_warning">Using this service over your mobile network connection may result in additional fees from your wireless provider if you do not have an unlimited data plan. Download updates now?</string>
    <string name="title_download_wifi">Download via Wi-Fi or cable</string>
    <string name="msg_download_wifi">Downloading will start when Wi-Fi or Internet pass-through are connected, and will pause if they disconnect.</string>
    <string name="msg_download_later">Your phone will check for updates at the next scheduled time. You can check for updates manually in Settings.</string>
    <string name="msg_download_later_no_ui">Your phone will check for updates at the next scheduled time.</string>
    <string name="title_update_corrupted">Update is corrupted</string>
    <string name="msg_update_corrupted">"The downloaded system software update is corrupted.
Do you want to download it again?"</string>
    <string name="btn_download">Download</string>
    <string name="title_no_sd_card">SD card not ready</string>
    <string name="msg_no_sd_card">You need an SD card to download the system update. Please insert an SD card and press OK to start the download, or press Cancel to exit.</string>
    <string name="title_no_space">Not enough space</string>
    <string name="msg_no_space">"You don't have enough space remaining on your storage card. Please delete some content or applications to make at least %s MB of free space. 
Tap \"Settings\" below to make more free space."</string>
    <string name="msg_no_space_no_ui">"You don't have enough space remaining on your storage card. Please delete some content or applications to make at least %s MB of free space."</string>
    <string name="title_save_error">Error saving update</string>
    <string name="msg_save_error">An error occurred while saving the system update to your SD card. The download process cannot be completed. Please replace your SD card and check for updates again in Settings, under About phone.</string>
    <string name="msg_save_error_no_ui">An error occurred while saving the system update to your SD card. The download process cannot be completed.</string>
    <string name="title_install">Install system software update</string>
    <string name="msg_install_prompt">Would you like to install the following system software update?</string>
    <string name="label_install_now">Install now</string>
    <string name="label_install_later">Install later</string>
    <string name="msg_install_later">You can start installation from the notifications bar at any time.</string>
    <string name="title_cancel_installation">Cancel installation</string>
    <string name="msg_cancel_installation">This will stop the update process and delete the downloaded update file from your phone. Cancel now?</string>
    <string name="title_update_ready">System update is ready</string>
    <string name="msg_update_ready">Tap to install the system update</string>
    <string name="summary_periodic_checkin_off">This feature has been disabled by your provider</string>
    <string name="msg_battery_low">"The system update is ready, but your phone's battery is too low to install it. Please charge the battery to 35% or more and start installation later."</string>
    <string name="msg_install_no_sd_card">You need an SD card to back up your data. Please insert an SD card and press OK to continue, or press Cancel to skip the backup.</string>
    <string name="msg_install_no_space">There is not enough free space on your SD card to back up your data. Please replace your SD card and press OK to continue, or press Cancel to skip the backup.</string>
    <string name="msg_telephony_warning">You will not be able to use your phone or make emergency calls during the upgrade. Please do not turn off your phone, or remove the battery or storage card during the upgrade.</string>
    <string name="msg_backup_warning">If you have enabled data backup in Settings, some of your data and settings, such as messages, bookmarks and Wi-Fi passwords, will be preserved, but we suggest that you back up your data before installation.</string>
    <string name="btn_discard">Discard</string>
    <string name="progress_label_verify">Verifying package</string>
    <string name="title_install_complete">System software update</string>
    <string name="msg_install_complete">Congratulations!</string>
    <string name="msg_install_complete_info">Your phone has been updated successfully to version %s.</string>
    <string name="download_state_paused">Download is paused because Wi-Fi or Internet pass-through connection was lost.</string>
    <string name="title_update_available">System update is available</string>
    <string name="msg_update_available">Tap to download the system update</string>
    <string name="toast_download_progress">Downloading software updates. Check progress in the notifications list.</string>
    <string name="title_battery_low">Battery low</string>
    <string name="title_storage_full">Storage full</string>
    <string name="msg_storage_full">"The system update is ready, but you don't have enough free space remaining in your phone's storage. Please uninstall some applications to make at least %sMB of free space.

Tap \"Settings\" below to manage your apps. You can start installation later from the notifications list."</string>
    <string name="msg_install_no_sd">Please insert the SD card on which you stored the downloaded system software update.</string>
    <string name="msg_install_share_sd">Unable to read the SD card on which you stored the downloaded system software update because it is being used by your PC as USB storage. Disconnect USB to access your SD card.</string>
    <string name="msg_download_share_sd">Your SD card is not available to store the system software update because it is being used by your PC as USB storage. Disconnect USB and press OK to start the download, or press Cancel to exit.</string>
    <string name="title_install_miss_file">Update is missing</string>
    <string name="msg_install_miss_file">The downloaded system software update is missing from your SD card. Do you want to download it again?</string>
    <string name="title_progress_paused">Download paused</string>
    <string name="acu_status_update">Update</string>
    <string name="acu_status_new">New</string>
    <string name="acu_title_update_available">Application updates available</string>
    <string name="acu_msg_update_available">Tap to download the application updates</string>
    <string name="acu_msg_download_prompt">Would you like to install the following application updates?</string>
    <string name="acu_btn_detail">Detail</string>
    <string name="acu_application_detail">Application updates detail</string>
    <string name="acu_application_update">Application updates</string>
    <string name="acu_installing">Installing...</string>
    <string name="acu_installing_title">Installing updates</string>
    <string name="acu_installing_msg">Installing app</string>
    <string name="acu_success_message">Installation completed successfully.</string>
    <string name="kilobyte">KB</string>
    <string name="acu_cache_fill_title">Temporary space full</string>
    <string name="acu_cache_fill_message">"Unable to continue to update your software because there is not enough free temporary space in your phone's storage.

You may try restart your phone and check for software updates again in Settings, under About phone."</string>
    <string name="acu_download_fail_title">Download failed</string>
    <string name="acu_download_fail_message">"An error occurred while downloading the software updates.

You may check for software updates again in Settings, under About phone."</string>
    <string name="acu_file_corrupted_title">File corrupted</string>
    <string name="acu_file_corrupted_message">"There is a problem with the downloaded software update file. Unable to continue installation.

You may check for software updates again in Settings, under About phone."</string>
    <string name="acu_storage_full_message">"Unable to continue to update your software because there is not enough free space in your phone's storage.
Please uninstall some apps to make more space.

Tap \"Settings\" below to manage your apps. You may check for software updates again in Settings, under About phone."</string>
    <string name="acu_install_fail_title">Unable to complete the installation</string>
    <string name="acu_install_fail_message">"An error occurred while installing the software updates.

You may check for software updates again in Settings, under About phone."</string>
    <string name="acu_success_finish_message">The updates have been successfully installed on your phone.</string>
    <string name="title_cid_not_match">Variant system version</string>
    <string name="msg_cid_not_match">We have determined that your phone may be running a modified version of its system software. For your protection, we cannot update your phone. Please revert your phone to the official HTC system software to update your phone. If you did not modify your system software or would like help reverting your system, please contact us via the support section at www.htc.com.</string>
    <string name="msg_sd_card_read_only">Your SD card is not available to store the software update because it is mounted as read-only mode. You may reboot your phone and check for updates again in Settings, under About phone.</string>
    <string name="msg_not_allow_3g">The action works only in Wi-Fi or cable connection. Please turn on the Wi-Fi in Settings, or use the cable connection to a computer.</string>
    <string name="encrypted_package_fail_title">Encrypted package</string>
    <string name="key_server_fail_message">Failed to connect to the key server. Check connection and try again.</string>
    <string name="no_authority_fail_message">Your phone is not authorized to get the decryption key.</string>
    <string name="key_invalid_fail_message">The decryption key is invalid.</string>
    <string name="outside_intranet_fail_title">Outside Intranet</string>
    <string name="outside_intranet_fail_message">The update is located on the testing server and not accessible from outside the company Intranet. Please try download again when you are back to Intranet.</string>
    <string name="download_state_connection_paused">Download is paused because your data connection was lost.</string>
    <string name="download_state_roaming_paused">Download is paused because your data connection is in roaming mode. Please use Wi-Fi or cable.</string>
    <string name="category_software_update_srmmary">In progress...</string>
    <string name="title_no_sd_card_internal">Phone storage not ready</string>
    <string name="msg_no_sd_card_internal">Your phone storage is not available to store the system software update because it is being used by your PC as USB storage. Disconnect USB and press OK to start the download, or press Cancel to exit.</string>
    <string name="msg_no_space_internal">"You don't have enough space remaining on your phone storage. Please delete some content or applications to make at least %s MB of free space. 
Tap \"Settings\" below to make more free space."</string>
    <string name="msg_save_error_internal">An error occurred while saving the system update to your phone storage. The download process cannot be completed.</string>
    <string name="msg_install_no_sd_internal">Unable to read the phone storage on which you stored the downloaded system software update because it is being used by your PC as USB storage. Disconnect USB to access your phone storage.</string>
    <string name="msg_install_miss_file_internal">The downloaded system software update is missing from your phone storage. Do you want to download it again?</string>
    <string name="msg_sd_card_read_only_internal">Your phone storage is not available to store the software update because it is mounted as read-only mode. You may reboot your device and check for updates again in Settings, under About phone.</string>
    <string name="title_download_wifi_noIPT">Download via Wi-Fi only</string>
    <string name="label_download_via_wifi_noIPT">Download via Wi-Fi</string>
    <string name="msg_download_wifi_noIPT">Download will start when Wi-Fi is connected, and will pause if Wi-Fi disconnects.</string>
    <string name="download_state_paused_noIPT">Download is paused because Wi-Fi connection was lost.</string>
    <string name="download_state_roaming_paused_noIPT">Download is paused because your data connection is in roaming mode. Please use Wi-Fi.</string>
    <string name="btn_later">Later</string>
    <string name="title_update_canceled">Update canceled</string>
    <string name="msg_update_canceled">You can find canceled updates later in Settings > About phone > Software updates.</string>
    <string name="title_cota_update">Personalize update</string>
    <string name="title_cota_available">Personalize update available</string>
    <string name="msg_cota_available">Tap to download the update</string>
    <string name="title_cota_download">A Personalize update is available</string>
    <string name="msg_cota_download_prompt">Would you like to download the update?</string>
    <string name="msg_cota_storage_full">"You don't have enough free space remaining in your phone's storage. Please delete some content or applications to make at least %s free space.
Tap \"Settings\" below to manage your apps."</string>
    <string name="msg_cota_file_corrupted">"There is a problem with the downloaded software update file. Unable to continue installation.
Do you want to download it again?"</string>
    <string name="title_cota_install">Install Personalize update</string>
    <string name="msg_cota_install_prompt">Would you like to install the update now?</string>
    <string name="title_cota_install_notify">Personalize update is ready</string>
    <string name="msg_cota_install_notify">Tap to install the update.</string>
    <string name="title_restart">Application updates download complete</string>
    <string name="msg_restart">Your phone downloaded application updates and needs to be restarted to complete the update process. Please press Restart now.</string>
    <string name="msg_notification_restart">Tap to restart your phone.</string>
</resources>
