<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="url_load_unsuccessful_message">Your tablet is not connected to a mobile data service. To view this information now, go to %s in a web browser.</string>
    <string name="activation_text">Touch <b>Activate</b>" to activate your mobile service now. (It may take a couple of minutes.)

Or touch "<b>Skip</b> to set up your tablet using a Wi-Fi connection instead.</string>
    <string name="activation_skip_confirmation">"Until you activate your mobile data service, most of your tablet's features won't work.

If you prefer to skip now, you can activate later in Settings."</string>
    <string name="activation_failure_text">"Your mobile data service couldn't be activated. This may be a temporary problem.

If you prefer to skip now, be sure to activate later in Settings. Until you activate, most of your tablet's features won't work."</string>
    <string name="activation_failure_text_gen">"Your mobile data service couldn't be activated. This may be a temporary problem and may be solved by restarting the tablet."</string>
    <string name="activation_spc_failure_text">An error occurred that requires your tablet to be shut down and restarted before another activation attempt can be made. Your tablet will shut down automatically in 60 seconds or you can touch <b>Shut down now</b>".

Once your tablet is shut down, press its Power button to restart it."</string>
    <string name="name_activity_title">This tablet belongs to...</string>
    <string name="name_activity_text">The tablet uses your name to personalise some apps.</string>
    <string name="tos_agreement_text">"You agree that your tablet may receive and install updates from Google.

Your use of this tablet is subject to the privacy policy and other terms. "<annotation id="learn_more">Learn more</annotation></string>
    <string name="setup_complete_message">Your tablet is set up and ready to use.</string>
    <string name="sim_missing_text">Read the instructions that came with your tablet.</string>
</resources>
